DO YOU HAVE ANYONE ELSE TO TALK TO?
I JUST WANT TO STOP BEING INVISIBLE.
SARA'S BIRTHDAY PARTY
THEME?
GLITTER, YOUR BODY, AND SKIMPY CLOTHING
MOM: BEEN INVITED TO THE PARTY YET?
PLAYLIST FOR CHLOE
PLAYLIST ADDED TO YOUR MUSIC
YEAH, I WAS INVITED.
COME ON. TALK TO ME.
YOU NEED TO KNOW THE TRUTH
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
INTERMEDIARY: AS SOON AS
THE FIRST PAYMENT IS IN MY ACCOUNT,
I'LL ORDER THE EVICTION.
WE'RE STAYING
ART AND HOUSING FOR ALL
OCCUPIED SOCIAL CENTER
SELF-MANAGED SOCIAL CENTER
LEAVE PHONES HERE
NEW MESSAGE
COME TO SARA'S PARTY.
WE CAN TALK ABOUT STARTING OVER.
IVÁN'S BEEN THROUGH A LOT,
AND HE'S STILL SUFFERING.
LET'S LEAVE HIM ALONE.
DELETE MESSAGE
CANCEL - DELETE
DELETE
NEW MESSAGE
NO BATTERY
POLICE
NO TO SPECULATION
I JUST WANT TO STOP BEING INVISIBLE.
PLAYLIST FOR CHLOE BY ERIC
YOU'VE BEEN ADDED
TO LAS ENCINAS SELF-DEFENSE GROUP
CLASSES START TOMORROW .
SPORTS AREA
Subtitle translation by: Toni Navarro,
Meredith Cannella